Jiang Yu!
Jiang Yu.
It's okay.
Don't be afraid.
I've already called the police.
-Jiang Yu.
-Are you okay?
-Be careful.
-Jiang Yu.
♪In the darkness where there is no light,♪
You got hurt.
♪at the end of every lonely night,♪
Go.
♪now my heart is beating once again.♪
Go to the wedding as planned.
I'm fine.
My leg is...
♪Finally I'm breathing past the pain.♪
just a little off.
Ahao will come to pick me up later.
We just need to proceed as planned.
♪In the winter breeze I feel your breath♪
♪waken up my soul from frozen death,♪
My bride,
♪like a miracle you came in view.♪
go win back everything that's yours.
Take back what belongs to you.
♪At the edge of this breaking world,♪
♪you're the only one
who brought the light.♪
♪Because it's you,♪
I will definitely
make He Mu pay the price.
♪all my sadness♪
♪fading out of sight.♪
♪In your arms I'm born again and new.♪
Wait for me.
Go now.
[Dearest Episode12]
Jiang Yu.
Jiang Yu!
Dear relatives and friends,
I'm really sorry to
announce that
due to unforeseen circumstances,
today's wedding must be canceled.
Jianan,
what's wrong with you?
Jianan.
My wedding
is not over.
My stepfather, He Mu,
plotted to harm my husband and me.
But I survived.
So,
my wedding is not over.
Play the recording.
Mr. He, what do you want us to do?
Blow up their wedding car
and leave them with nowhere to rest.
Jianan,
why do you use a fake recording
to frame Dad?
Today is your wedding.
It's a good day.
Please don't make this kind of joke, okay?
Where did the explosion happen today?
The whole city is peaceful.
There was no explosion at all!
Mr. He.
Mr. He,
please come with us.
Sir,
there must be some mistake.
Mr. He,
all your accomplices
have all been arrested.
We have solid evidence
that prove you plotted to murder
Wen Jianan and Jiang Yu.
The evidence also shows
you are suspected of involvement in
the murder of Jiang Yuqing.
Jianan,
are you doing the same thing to me
as you did to your ex?
Hiring people to put on a show?
If you don't want to marry Jiang Yu,
just tell Dad.
Even if he is the boss of Cloudsea,
you don't have to be afraid of him.
How dare you mention Jiang Yu?
He's your own son.
What are you talking about?
You had your own son get
close to me on purpose.
Just to take over the Wen family.
Grandpa gave you the group.
Mom gave you her heart.
I gave you all my trust!
We were so good to you.
Why did you do this?
I will love you for him.
You used your own son to
play with my feelings
and move into home.
Just to take over the Wen family.
Why did you do this to us?
You're crazy.
What nonsense are you talking about?
You wolf-hearted schemer.
No, you have no heart at all!
You don't deserve to be a good husband,
let alone a good father!
You're crazy!
Everyone, let me explain!
Don't listen to her nonsense!
Go explain it to the police.
Mrs. Wen, please calm down!
So it really was you who killed him.
Xin, who are you talking about?
Who do you mean?
Chenghan.
My love, from twenty years ago, Chenghan!
You gave our volcanic stone ring
to your first love,
and then married me.
You really disgust me!
I didn't!
Go pay for him with your life.
Dad, Dad, save me.
I did so much for you.
Shut up!
You've been scheming against
the Wen family and me all along!
We don't have a son-in-law like you!
Take him away!
Mr. He, please.
Come find me.
I will tell you the truth,
including who your biological father is.
Jianan.
Are you okay?